Mythica: The Necromancer is a fantasy, action,
adventure film directed by A. Todd Smith.
The young wizard Marek is forced to lead her band of would-be heroes on a mission
for the corrupt Thieves Guild, which has taken her friend hostage.
Their journey will take them straight into the wicked
clutches of Szorlok, their greatest enemy.
Marek, played by Melanie Stone.
Thane, played by Adam Johnson.
Dagen, played by Jake Stormoen.
Teela, played by Nicola Posener.
Betylla, played by Philip Brodie.
Szorlok, played by Matthew Mercer.
Mythica is a series of primarily direct-to-video fantasy films.
The films are produced by Arrowstorm Entertainment, with first film Mythica: A Quest for
Heroes being partly funded by a Kickstarter campaign that collected $94,294.
There are six films in the Mythica series, all produced and
co-written by Jason Faller and Kynan Griffin.
The films star Melanie Stone as Marek, an escaped slave girl and budding magician, and co-star Kevin Sorbo as Gojun Pye the magician who trains
her, along with Adam Johnson, Jake Stormoen, and Nicola Posener as those that team up with Marek on various quests together.
The film explores themes of magic, sword, sorcery, necromancer.